<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ahmed Massoud DevOps Project</title>
    <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-047-advanced/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ahmed Massoud DevOps Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-047-advanced/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About learning</title>
      <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-047-advanced/posts/about-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-047-advanced/posts/about-learning/</guid>
      <description>Learning 047 The learning in this course was fun, it was not very challenging, the videos that was presented through the oreilly course was easily digestible and not very difficult, I learnt from it the concept of DevOps, continuous delivery continuous deployment and integration, I got a chance to explore and compare the old apporch of software development and the new approch using DevOps, and how DevOps removes the huge time gape between the development and the deployment and provide very fast results and product for the customer which probably makes more moeny for software companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About This course</title>
      <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-047-advanced/posts/about-this-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-047-advanced/posts/about-this-course/</guid>
      <description>This course 047 Devops has been this buzz word that everyone is talking about these days, I have been thinking about reading and studying Devops since the beginning of this year but I did not have enough time and when I stumbled upon this course on Oodi, I decided to take the course right away without hesitation, because through this course I did what I have been wanting to do for month but being lazy instead.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>